http://www.eastwaylock.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy | Eastway Lock & Key, Inc.
Privacy Policy | Eastway Lock & Key, Inc.
Posted by Charlotte Locksmith April 4th, 2016
We want you to know how seriously we take your privacy, so please read our privacy policy, which we’re sure will address any worries you may have:
If you submit your information we’ll keep it for the purposes of contacting you and we won’t share it with anyone else.
We don’t spam…but if you submit your email address to us you may receive an email from us from time to time. You will have the option to unsubscribe from these at any time.
We don’t:
Sell, lease or otherwise disseminate your information
Contact you after you have unsubscribed from our email list
We do:
Use your feedback to make our sites and customer service better
Encrypt sensitive data and use other methods to protect your particulars
Here’s a bit more from our legal friends:
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified on 31-MAR-2016
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us via the contact us page on this website.
Contact Us Today!
Your Name*Your Email*
Your Phone*Your Message*
About Us At Eastway Lock & Key, Inc., we are your trusted company for residential and commercial locksmith services and other security solutions in Charlotte, North Carolina. Visit our showroom or call us today!
Hours Of Operation
Eastway Lock & Key, Inc.Mon 9:00 am - 5:00 pm
Tue 9:00 am - 5:00 pm
Wed 9:00 am - 5:00 pm
Thur 10:00 am - 5:00 pm
Fri 9:00 am - 5:00 pm
Sat 9:00 am - 2:00 pm
Contact Us
Eastway Lock & Key, Inc.
3807 Monroe Rd Charlotte, NC
28205
Telephone:
(704) 347-1088
661 Robert M Grissom Pkwy
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577
Telephone: (843) 626-3180
Eastway Lock & Key, Inc.
Service Area Charlotte, Ballantyne, Blakeney, Stonecrest, Fort Mill, Concord, Indian Trail, Huntersville, Mount Holly, Marvin, Rock Hill, Waxhaw
Beach location – Myrtle Beach, Surfside Beach, Garden City, North Myrtle, Carolina Forest, Little River, Conway, Murrell’s Inlet, Pawleys Island and Horry County and surrounding areas
Hardware, Charlotte, NCSecurity, Charlotte, NCAuto Locksmith, Charlotte, NCKeys, Charlotte, NCAutomotive Locksmith, Charlotte, NCSafe Services, Charlotte, NCSafe Products, Charlotte, NCDoor Hardware, Charlotte, NCDoor Services, Charlotte, NCAccess Control, Charlotte, NCWooden Doors, Charlotte, NCCCTV, Charlotte, NCFire Alarms, Charlotte, NCDoor Locks, Charlotte, NCDoors, Charlotte, NCHigh-Security Lock, Charlotte, NCLocksmith, Charlotte, NCCommercial Doors, Charlotte, NCCar Keys, Charlotte, NCTransponder, Charlotte, NCCar Opening, Charlotte, NCMetal Doors, Charlotte, NCCommercial Alarm System, Charlotte, NCLocksmith Services, Charlotte, NCSafes, Charlotte, NC
Recent Locksmith Posts
How Video Security Can Benefit Your Business
Calling an Auto Locksmith? Follow These Safety Tips! [infographic]
